when i show my face
you're probably going to have some
questions
why are my b-dubs and on top of that
why have i got a bald green face some of
you will already know the answer to this
question and it's basically because we
did a very
very good thing
round here at the back of the mansion i
can quite happily reveal
we've actually done some work on it
b-dubs scar ren and i all worked on the
back of the mansion on a live stream
for charity and i'm very pleased to say
we absolutely smashed the goal on this
live stream we said if we reached our
goal we would all swap skins and then
b-dubs chat said take green's waffle
away
so
that's exactly what happened
it's also fair to say that things got
pretty weird and we started re-enacting
famous star wars scenes
you are my brother green
[Laughter]
i'm not even gonna comment on that so
now i'm left as b-dubs for the start of
this episode
i plan on swapping back
but i won't be able to do that until the
others get online so everyone's just
gonna have to be a little bit confused
as to why
i'm b dubs but let's take a look at what
we've got for the back of the mansion so
we didn't actually get much detailing
done and that was because we very much
didn't have much of a plan however we
did get quite a lot of the terraining
done which is a huge task we spent about
three hours doing this and we got quite
a lot done the charity was for sos
africa who we've worked with in the past
and i'm really pleased to say it was
super successful so a massive thank you
to absolutely everybody that turned up
and even more so to those who donated it
will go a really long way so let's crack
on with this episode where we will be
officially i can't i don't think i can
talk to the cameras b-dubs
i i don't i it does it none of it feels
right none of it feels right so today
we're going to be attempting to open the
hc bbs now you'll know from last episode
that that is pretty much complete so my
task for the start of this episode is to
start filling it out
with actual shulker boxes and filling
those shulker boxes with actual stuff
then placing them all around the hc bbs
impulse did volunteer to help me with
this task because it's going to be quite
a difficult one so this is basically
what a shulker box will look like it'll
have varying degrees of junk or useful
things and of course they have to try
and just take as much as possible and
avoid things like dirt and then there's
a tiny little bit
of decoration to do
in the final segment and then we will be
100 ready i can't wait to get this thing
i'm still b-dubs i can't i can't deal
with this do you know what i would
rather have
bald green than this so
i'm gonna go and fill up the htbs with
some very useful and not so useful
shulker boxes full of stuff soon after
this i actually came into contact with
b-dubs and i was recording the screen
but not my voice so this is pretty much
what happened i called him hideous he
called me gorgeous
and then we decided to swap skins back
the only way we know how on the
hermitcraft server running at each other
extremely quickly
until our faces smushed together then i
called him gorgeous and then we went our
own separate ways
setting this thing up
filling all of those boxes
and finishing the hcbs
took me a full day i have completely
lost my mind this this song is stuck in
my head forever
but it is now done full done so i'm
ready to open i i didn't actually
include a lot of the process because
this has taken me so long i you know
this is like what three or four episodes
in and i was like oh you know
i'm sick of it you're sick of it
everyone's sick of it let's just get
this thing done and this will be our
final test because it's ready now
welcome when it comes to the actual
timing of this
[Music]
i'm so used to this now
so here's the thing about the timing
it's not perfect and it never will be
every time i've done this and i've
tested this about 40 million times now
the timing is different every single
time i think there's a bit of server lag
there's a bit of rail inconsistency i'm
not sure but it's about as close as i
can possibly get it i've done a bunch of
improvements
and generally just tidied the thing up
and if we can find a box you'll see that
they are all full of stuff
and it's pretty easy to get stuff if you
know where the good boxes are you will
find
some goodies especially there's one
there high value see there's some
diamonds and such in there i don't
really want to spoil what's in here
because it's not just items there's some
other things as well i wonder if i think
there's a there's a secret somewhere in
here you can't see these ones too well
but yeah there's some really good stuff
up for grabs poultry man and i of course
finished off building the last room
which is the the hippie area 77
reference
and we're starting to come to the end
where we go through
the final bit
[Music]
ah see the timing
timing was off
dang it but anyway that just goes to
show we're ready all i need to do now is
set up oh an impulse buys has got the
rest of his stuff set up as well it's
pretty bad timing because
this season is actually coming to an end
for me personally that doesn't mean that
no one else will be making videos this
isn't the finale i've got some other
stuff planned for the finale but overall
i feel like this season has been amazing
and for me
there's not a lot left that i would like
to do or achieve so i don't know whether
there's going to be one more episode or
two more episodes but
i have to tell you right now
we are very much approaching the end of
this season for me on the green channel
only but we will get to all of that
stuff
at the finale we can we can reminisce
and we can go through everything we've
been through together
later on
for now we need we need to get this
finished but that's why it's pretty bad
timing right because if this is the last
few episodes how many people are
actually going to play how how how much
enjoyment am i going to get out of this
and also am i actually going to make any
diamonds in time for the end of the
season so what i'm going to do now is
get a hc bbs
information board built
right here okay i can't believe it this
project is actually done oh no
i
just put item frames here
and pressing this button explodes them
okay i'm not using the tnt launcher
anymore i'm just going to put i'm just
going to put two signs there because i
just lost a diamond doing that okay so
right let's go through this welcome to
hcbbs hermitcraft big barge sweep the
game is explained when you play place 16
diamonds in the chest below and grab a
minecart then read the technical signs
on the right
boring
place your minecart and enter it
play the disc and enjoy so it's fairly
straightforward but i'm pretty sure
people are going to get this wrong it's
as simple as oh no i lost the disc as
well
oh that is
tragic i'm gonna have to visit beefy's
music emporium and pay for another cat
disc and
done the whole thing
is ready to go
i i honestly don't know what to do with
myself now i've just finished one of the
biggest projects of this season for me
it may not seem like it on the front of
it but this this build this mini game
the shopping experience has taken me one
of the longest amounts of time ever
whether it was building the extension to
the barge or all of the excavating and
building this complex thing here if i
had a nickel for every time impulse and
i built a roller coaster themed track
i'd have two nickels which isn't a lot
but it's weird that it happened twice
yeah i said the thing i said the thing
because if you remember from the end of
last season we did the ride of your life
and then at the end of this season we've
done the hcbs so
maybe this is
next time you see us building one of
these together with impulse you know
that the end of the season might be
around the corner
don't take that literally it was just a
funny coincidence oh no oh no oh no oh
phew oh no please
oh no
what do i do
for winner only that's me oh well i got
a bit of a bonus thing here oh no this
is
terrible but
good oh i've won so much i i o beat up
so much money um
not quite sure how to pay for this and
also this is terrible news oh geez okay
so how many did i win
one
two
three four
five
six
so i need to give b dubs
30 diamond blocks 30 diamond blocks
clearly no one wanted some land in
aquita dudes i don't know what to do
with this i don't need all this land why
did i even buy it in the first place i
know i have an idea let's get rid of all
this you've seen me pay i've added it on
the pile here 30 diamond blocks nice and
shiny and new
and a little bit reluctantly given so
what i'm gonna do here is i'm gonna find
some odd things like coal that'll do
charcoal if i got any more coal
some real junk items okay like this and
what i'll do is i'll rename the coal
free plot in aqua town because i don't
know what to do with them i fully intend
on trying to get rid of these
in a good way so if i can find one of my
high value boxes for example there's one
up here
i'll just replace one of the string with
a free plot in aqua town and they're
going to have to hover over that to be
able to get it so all i've got to do is
find
six high value boxes and swap out some
items there we go
i have hidden them
amongst the hc bbs perfect way
to get rid of it and i mean it's it's
five blocks worth of value really five
diamond blocks they're probably one of
the top tier prizes there's not a lot
left i can do at the barge to be honest
with you it's it's come as far as it can
at this point and also i want to point
out i don't know how long this mistake
has been here but it's
quite embarrassing really so you know
i'm pretty famous for selling some sand
sand one diamond for two stacks
sand one diamond
for one stack
huh
i don't know how long
there's been two separate prices
but some someone bought the sand out of
this one
at quite the premium
and i have no idea who but that's quite
funny i'm gonna leave it like that i'm
gonna leave it it's it's funny it's near
the end of the season those of you that
download the world when it goes public
you can you can enjoy that and that i've
somehow most people didn't make that
mistake by the way even though there's
been two different prices they've paid
the the lower of the two which is quite
enjoyable so i can now declare hc bbs
open for business
right there's a lot of things that we
need to do before we wrap up this season
we can't leave things unfinished and the
big thing
that is totally gonna bother me if i
don't finish it and it's it's not this
it's not the pile of mess that i've made
outside it's actually some of the
undetailed bits of
the mansion
so that is gonna be my big project i i'm
okay with sir leaving certain things
behind but not others so for example i
really love
the interior
that is in here the diamond chandelier
all of this i love it it works what i'm
not worried about i'm not i'm not that
fussed that this isn't done and i'm not
that fussed that this isn't done i
really didn't need the extra villagers
and all that kind of stuff so yes it
went unused but
at the end of the day
i probably left it too late i'd already
got everything i needed to so lessons
learned for sure but i'm happy with this
interior here
but i'm not happy
with the state of things
over here
not detailed blank
no trees so what i'm going to try and
lighting error
what i'm going to try and do for the end
of this episode is try and clean up and
build some details
into these parts and see what we can do
all right let's go
[Music]
that
is a lot better
it's actually not quite what i wanted to
do i think i've got some real terraining
issues here and i might actually ask
scar
if he could give me a bit of a hand with
this because i'm not quite sure where i
went wrong i think
it needs a bit more dirt transition
between the two
but scar will be able to point me in the
right direction you see how there's a
there's a pretty poor transition from
dirt to stone i think that's what looks
a bit wrong but i'm pretty sure scar
wouldn't mind giving me a little bit of
a hand with that so overall though i
think that has helped i mean you're not
meant to look at it directly and pick it
apart but when you look at the mansion
as a whole
it kind of helps blend it all in down to
the bottom and you can really see the
difference here where i've just spammed
bone meal compared to this side where
there's actually more trees and
waterfalls and stuff it all kind of
works together for many years now i have
co-owned and worked on a minecraft
server called wincraft it's an mmorpg
so you do quests you level up and you go
on adventures and recently we have
actually released a bit of an update we
frequently update the server as much as
we can and along with my co-owners
salted and jamla we continue to work on
this server over the years and salted
one of the co-owners has kindly made a
specific video for me to show you guys
and here it is now just a disclaimer i
do co-own this so any advertising on
this channel i do financially benefit
from so here check this out he made this
really cool custom trailer and it's
amazing so take a look at wincraft
[Music]
[Applause]
so if you want to give wincraft a go
there is some information in the
description with the ip it is only for
java edition of minecraft we're not on
bedrock at all so sorry bedrock people
and thank you to salted for making that
video for me right well that is pretty
much all i have time for today i really
am starting to scrape the bottom of the
barrel on what needs to be done
for the rest of the season so i have
just a few more things to check off i
want to do some minor improvements
around the front of the mansion and then
some big improvements i've run out of
rockets and some big improvements
to the back which actually scar is
supposed to do so we probably helped him
more than we helped me i think just some
casual detailing to this and the whole
thing
will be dunzo all there is left to say
is thank you very much for watching
thank you to everyone who donated to the
charity and thank you for watching that
little video at the end i shall see you
in the next episode which will likely be
a very special finale
it's going to be
well it's going to be as epic as i can
make it i think we're going to play some
of tangos among us we're going to play
some tarjay at cubs base and we're going
to do a big world tour and hopefully try
and finish off what's left at the
mansion and we'll wrap this whole thing
up so please please please tune in and
let me know how you felt about this
season in the comments below thank you
very much for watching and good
bye
you